export const operationsAndNames = [
    {
      operation: "+", 
      name: "Addition", 
    }, 
    {
      operation: "-", 
      name: "Subtraction", 
    }, 
    {
      operation: "*", 
      name: "Multiplication", 
    }, 
    {
      operation: "/", 
      name: "Division", 
    }, 
    ]


  
    export const soundsAndNames = [
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "a",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "cat", back: "c-a-t" },
          { front: "bat", back: "b-a-t" },
          { front: "sat", back: "s-a-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "a",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "cape", back: "c-a-p-e" },
          { front: "rate", back: "r-a-t-e" },
          { front: "date", back: "d-a-t-e" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "e",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "pet", back: "p-e-t" },
          { front: "set", back: "s-e-t" },
          { front: "bet", back: "b-e-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "e",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "tee", back: "t-e-e" },
          { front: "see", back: "s-e-e" },
          { front: "bee", back: "b-e-e" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "i",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "mit", back: "m-i-t" },
          { front: "bit", back: "b-i-t" },
          { front: "sit", back: "s-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "i",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "time", back: "t-i-m-e" },
          { front: "lime", back: "l-i-m-e" },
          { front: "fine", back: "f-i-n-e" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "o",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "pot", back: "p-o-t" },
          { front: "bot", back: "b-o-t" },
          { front: "hot", back: "h-o-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "o",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "pole", back: "p-o-l-e" },
          { front: "sold", back: "s-o-l-d" },
          { front: "told", back: "t-o-l-d" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "u",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "cut", back: "c-u-t" },
          { front: "but", back: "b-u-t" },
          { front: "mut", back: "m-u-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "u",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "cute", back: "c-u-t-e" },
          { front: "mute", back: "m-u-t-e" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "short",
        name: "y",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "yes", back: "y-e-s" },
          { front: "you", back: "y-o-u" },
          { front: "yip", back: "y-i-p" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "vowel",
        emphasis: "long",
        name: "y",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "my", back: "m-y" },
          { front: "by", back: "b-y" },
          { front: "fly", back: "f-l-y" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "b",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "bat", back: "b-a-t" },
          { front: "bet", back: "b-e-t" },
          { front: "bib", back: "b-i-b" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "c",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "cot", back: "c-o-t" },
          { front: "cut", back: "c-u-t" },
          { front: "cat", back: "c-a-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "d",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "led", back: "l-e-d" },
          { front: "med", back: "m-e-d" },
          { front: "red", back: "r-e-d" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "f",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "fun", back: "f-u-n" },
          { front: "fat", back: "f-a-t" },
          { front: "fit", back: "f-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "g",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "got", back: "g-o-t" },
          { front: "gut", back: "g-u-t" },
          { front: "gat", back: "g-a-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "h",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "hat", back: "h-a-t" },
          { front: "hit", back: "h-i-t" },
          { front: "hot", back: "h-o-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "j",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "jet", back: "j-e-t" },
          { front: "jam", back: "j-a-m" },
          { front: "job", back: "j-o-b" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "k",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "kit", back: "k-i-t" },
          { front: "kin", back: "k-i-n" },
          { front: "keg", back: "k-e-g" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "l",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "let", back: "l-e-t" },
          { front: "lot", back: "l-o-t" },
          { front: "lit", back: "l-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "m",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "mat", back: "m-a-t" },
          { front: "met", back: "m-e-t" },
          { front: "mit", back: "m-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "n",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "net", back: "n-e-t" },
          { front: "not", back: "n-o-t" },
          { front: "nit", back: "n-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "p",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "pat", back: "p-a-t" },
          { front: "pet", back: "p-e-t" },
          { front: "pit", back: "p-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "q",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "quit", back: "q-u-i-t" },
          { front: "quiz", back: "q-u-i-z" },
          { front: "quip", back: "q-u-i-p" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "r",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "rat", back: "r-a-t" },
          { front: "rot", back: "r-o-t" },
          { front: "rut", back: "r-u-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "s",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "sat", back: "s-a-t" },
          { front: "set", back: "s-e-t" },
          { front: "sit", back: "s-i-t" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "t",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "tap", back: "t-a-p" },
          { front: "tip", back: "t-i-p" },
          { front: "top", back: "t-o-p" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "v",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "vat", back: "v-a-t" },
          { front: "vet", back: "v-e-t" },
          { front: "vow", back: "v-o-w" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "w",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "wet", back: "w-e-t" },
          { front: "wit", back: "w-i-t" },
          { front: "won", back: "w-o-n" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "x",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "box", back: "b-o-x" },
          { front: "fix", back: "f-i-x" },
          { front: "tax", back: "t-a-x" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "y",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "yak", back: "y-a-k" },
          { front: "yet", back: "y-e-t" },
          { front: "yap", back: "y-a-p" }
        ]
      },
      {
        soundType: "consonant",
        emphasis: "",
        name: "z",
        flashcards: [
          { front: "zap", back: "z-a-p" },
          { front: "zig", back: "z-i-g" },
          { front: "zag", back: "z-a-g" }
        ]
      }
    ];